Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Pro-Animal Organizations, 31 linear feet
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 1 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 2 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 3 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 4 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 5 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 6 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 7 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - MD: Farm Animal Reform Movement (FARM) (MD) - 8 of 8 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - MD: Jewish Vegetarians of North America (MD) (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - MD: Metropolitan Ferret Friends, The (MD) (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - MD: Misty Manor Riding Stables (MD) (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Medical Research Modernization Commission - 1 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Medical Research Modernization Commission - 2 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Mexico: Asociación Activa Para la Suprecion de la Crueldad (Mexico) (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Mexico: Asociación de Lucha para Evitar la Crueldad con los Animales, A.C. (Mexico) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Mexico: Fuerzas Ecologicas de Liberación Animal (Mexico) (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Mexico: Group of 100 (Latin American Alliance) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Mexico: Peña Antitaurina Mexicana (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Michigan Greyhound Connection (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Mid-South Greyhound Adoption Option (Arkansas) (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Mill CreekFarm (Florida) (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Animal Rights Societies lists, clippings, etc.) (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous/ Pro-Animal Orgs. (CA) (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous/ Pro-Animal Orgs. (CA) (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous/ Pro-Animal Orgs. (CA) (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous/Pro animal Organizations (DC) - Empty File (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous/Rescue (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous/Various (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Mission: Wolf (Colorado) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Missouri Wild Horse League (Missouri) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Missourians Against Slaughtering Horses (MASH) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Monkey World (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery County Humane Society (MD)- 1 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Montgomery County Humane Society (MD)- 2 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery County Humane Society (MD)- 3 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Montgomery County Humane Society (MD)- 4 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Morris Animal Foundation (CO) (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Mountain Lion Coalition (CA) (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Mountain Lion Foundation (CA) (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Mountain States Horse Rescue and Rehab (Colorado) (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Namibia Cheetah Conservation Fund (Namibia) (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - National Activist Network (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - National Alliance for Animal Legislation (NAAL) - 1 of 4 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - National Alliance for Animal Legislation (NAAL) - 2 of 4 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - National Alliance for Animal Legislation (NAAL) - 3 of 4 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - National Alliance for Animal Legislation (NAAL) - 4 of 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - National Animal Control Association (KS) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - National Anti-Road Kill Project (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 1 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 2 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 3 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 4 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 5 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - National Anti-Vivisection Society (IL) - 6 of 6 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - National Association for Humane and Environmental Education (NAHEE) (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Humane Education (NAAHE) (DC) (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Nurses Against Vivisection (DC) - 1 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Nurses Against Vivisection (DC) - 2 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - National Audubon Society (CO)- 1 of 3 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - National Audubon Society (CO)- 2 of 3 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - National Audubon Society (CO)- 3 of 3 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - National Bird Feeding Society (IL) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - National Foundation for Animal Law (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - National Greyhound Adoption Program Michigan Affiliation (MI) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - National Resources Defense Council (NY) (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - National Wildlife Refuge Association (MD) (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - National Wildlife Rehabilitators Association (MN) (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (DC) (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Nature Conservancy (DC) (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Nature Conservancy of Maryland (MD) (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Nature of Wellness (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - NC: International Society for Cow Protection (NC) (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - NC: Miscellaneous (North Carolina) (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - NC: Zoophile News Network (North Carolina (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - NE: National Heart Savers Association (NE) (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Nederlandse Bond Tot Bestrijding van de Vivisectie (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Nederlandse Vereniging Tot Bescherming van Dieren (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Nesehnutí (Yugoslavia) (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Netherlands: Dutch Articles (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Netherlands: Miscellaneous/Dutch (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Netherlands: Pro Primates (Netherlands) (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Netherlands: Stichting De Poezenboot (Netherlands) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Netherlands: Stichting Lekker Dier (Netherlands) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Netherlands: Vegans International (Netherlands) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Network for Ani-Males and Females, Inc. (MD) (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - New Age Contacts (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - New England Anti-Vivisection Society (NEAVS) (MA) - 1 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - New England Anti-Vivisection Society (NEAVS) (MA) - 2 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - New England Anti-Vivisection Society (NEAVS) (MA) - 3 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - New York Turtle and Tortoise Society (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - New Zealand Anti-Vivisection Society (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - New Zealand: Save Animals from Experiments (SAFE) (NZ) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Ngare Sergoi Rhino Sanctuary (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - NH: Miscellaneous (NH) empty (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - NH: New Hampshire Doberman Rescue League (NH) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Nigeria: Miscellaneous (Nigeria) with long list of animal rights groups (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian Conservation Foundation (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - NJ: American Vegan Society (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - NJ: Beaver Defenders (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - NJ: Foundation for Animal Rights Advocacy (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - NJ: Humane Vegetarian Church (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - NJ: Marine Mammal Stranding Center (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - NJ: New Jersey Pot-Bellied Pig Association (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - NJ: North American Butterfly Association (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - NJ: Pit Perfect Rescue Operation (NJ) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - NM: Medical Care for Homeless Pets (NM) (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - NM: Public Lands Action Network (PLAN) (NM) (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - NM: Western Foundation for Raptor Conservation (NM) (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Norfolk SPCA (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - North American Bear Society (AZ) (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - North American Vegetarian Society, Inc. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - North American Wolf Foundation (MA) (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - North Shore Animal League - 1 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - North Shore Animal League 2 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Norway: Miscellaneous (Norway) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Norway: Noah (Norway) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Norway: Nordiska Samfundet (Norway) - 1 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Norway: Nordiska Samfundet (Norway) - 2 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Norway: Nordiska Samfundet (Norway) - 3 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - NV: Foundation Faith of God (NV) (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - NV: International Society for the Protection of Mustangs and Burros (NV) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - NV: Paladin’s Veterinary Welfare, Unltd. (NV) (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - NV: Tortoise Group (NV) (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - NV: United States Wild Horse and Burro Foundation (NV) (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - NV: Wild Horse Organized Assistance (NV) (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 1 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 2 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 3 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 4 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 5 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 6 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 7 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - NY: American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) (NY) - 8 of 8 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - NY: Animal Abusers Anonymous (NY) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - NY: Animal Rights International (NY) 1 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - NY: Animal Rights International (NY) 2 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - NY: Animal Rights International (NY) 3 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - NY: Animal Shelter Reform Committee (NY) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - NY: Argus Archives (NY) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - NY: Beauty without Cruelty—USA (NY) - 1 of 4 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - NY: Beauty without Cruelty—USA (NY) - 2 of 4 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - NY: Beauty without Cruelty—USA (NY) - 3 of 4 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - NY: Beauty without Cruelty—USA (NY) - 4 of 4 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - NY: Buffalo Greyhound Adoption, Inc. (NY) (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - NY: Carriage Horse Action Committee (NY) (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - NY: Civitas (NY) (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - NY: Coalition to Abolish the LD50 and Draize Tests (NY) (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - NY: Coalition to Protect Animals in Parks and Refuges (NY) (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - NY: Committee to Abolish Sport Hunting (NY) (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - NY: Digit Fund (NY) (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 1 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 2 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 3 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 4 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 5 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 6 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - NY: Farm Sanctuary (NY) 7 of 7 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - NY: Viva Vegie Society (NY) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Off Track Pets (NY) (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Ohio: Mobilization for Animals (Ohio)- 1 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Ohio: Mobilization for Animals (Ohio) - 2 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Ohio: Mobilization for Animals (Ohio) - 3 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Ohio: Mobilization for Animals (Ohio) - 4 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Ohio: National Society of Musicians for Animals (OH) (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ohio: Northern Ohio Association of Herpetologists (OH) (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ohio: Roger Troen Challenge Fund (OH) (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Ohio: The Feral Cat Coalition(OH) (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Ohio: United Animal Defenders (OH) (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Ol Pejata Rhino Sanctuary (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Operation Greyhound (CA) (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Opossum Society of California (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Options for Animals Foundation (IL) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - OR: Rat Allies (OR) (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - OR: The Great Ape Project USA (OR) (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Orangutan Foundation International (CA) (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Orangutan Project (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - PA: Adopt a Cow (PA) (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 1 of 8 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 2 of 8 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 3 of 8 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 4 of 8 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 5 of 8 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 7 of 8 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - PA: American Anti-Vivisection Society (AA-VS) (PA)- 8 of 8 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - PA: Animal Health Foundation (PA) (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - PA: AnimaLearn (PA) (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - PA: Delaware Valley Retired Racing Greyhound Association (PA) (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - PA: Evangelicals for Social Action (ESA) (PA) (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - PA: Humans Against Rabbit Exploitation (H.A.R.E.) (PA) (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - PA: Institute for Plant Based Nutrition (PA) (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 1 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 2 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 3 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 4 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 5 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - PA: International Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 6 of 6 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - PA: International Society for Cow Protection Inc. (ISCOWP) (PA) (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - PA: Jewish Vegetarians of the Delaware Valley (PA) (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - PA: National Greyhound Adoption Program (PA) (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - PA: Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - PA: Society for Animal Rights (PA) - 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - PA: Trans-Species Unlimited (TSU) (PA)-1 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - PA: Trans-Species Unlimited (TSU) (PA)-2 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - PA: Trans-Species Unlimited (TSU) (PA)-3 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - PA: Trans-Species Unlimited (TSU) (PA)-4 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - PA: Trans-Species Unlimited (TSU) (PA)-5 of 5 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Pacific Primate Sanctuary (Hawaii) (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Parque Nacional Portobelo (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Pegasus Foundation (LA/CA) (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Peninsula Humane Society (CA)-1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Peninsula Humane Society (CA)-2 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Peninsula Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, Inc. (VA) (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - People Protecting Primates (DC)missing folder (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - People, Animal, Love (PAL) (MD) (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS) (CA) (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Rain Forest Action Network (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Peru: Educacion para la Liberacion Animal (Peru) (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Peru: Miscellaneous (Peru) empty file (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Pet Network (CA) (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Pet Owners with AIDS/ARC Resource Services, Inc. (POWARS) (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Pet Savers Foundation (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - PETA Chapter newsletters - 1 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - PETA Chapter newsletters - 2 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Pets are Wonderful Support - San Diego (CA) (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Pets Are Wonderful Support/LA (PAWS; CA) (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Pets—DC (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine—Appeals (DC) (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine—Articles (DC) - 1 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine—Articles (DC) - 2 of 3 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine—Publications (DC) - 1 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine—Publications (DC) - 2 of 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Pig Hoppers (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Pigs Peace Sanctuary (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Pigs without Partners (CA) (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Pigs without Partners (Iowa) (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Poland: Animal Liberation Movement (Poland) (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Poland: Community of All Beings (Poland) (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Poland: Front Wyzwolenia Zwierzat (Poland) (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Poland: Green Brigades (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Poland: Klub Gaja (Poland) (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Poland: Miscellaneous (Poland) (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Poland: Polish Articles (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Political Animals (CA) (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Porpoise Rescue Foundation (CA) (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Portugal: Miscellaneous/Portuguese (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Portugal: Nucleo Portuguecirc;s de Estudo e Protecccedil;acirc;o da Vida Selvagem (Portuguese) (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Portugal: Portuguese articles (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Potbellied Pig Interest Group and Shelter (PIGS) (West Virginia) (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Potbelly Times (IL) (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Prairie Dog Rescue, Inc. (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Prairie National Wild Horse Refuge (Oklahoma) (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Predator Project (MT) (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Primarily Primates - 1 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Primarily Primates - 2 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Project Equus (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Providing Homes for America’s Remaining Mustangs (PHARM) (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Psychologists for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PsyETA) (MD)- 1 of 3 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Psychologists for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PsyETA) (MD) - 2 of 3 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Psychologists for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PsyETA) (MD) - 3 of 3 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Public Citizen (DC) (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Public Voice (DC) (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico: Asociacion Pro Albergue y Protección de Animales (APAYPA) (Puerto Rico) (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Puerto Rico: Bienestar (Puerto Rico) (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Puerto Rico: Humane Society of Puerto Rico (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Puerto Rico: Miscellaneous/Puerto Rico (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Puerto Rico: Protectores de Animales (Puerto Rico) (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Pure Food Campaign (DC) (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Rabbit Rescue Project (CA) (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Rachel Carson Council, Inc. (MD) (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Rainforest Action Network (CA) 2” (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Rainforest Reptile Refuge Society (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Red Wolf Sanctuary (Indiana) (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Redwings Horse Sanctuary (CA) (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Redwings Horse Sanctuary (UK) (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Reptile Defense Fund (LA) (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Rescue Ranch (Canada) (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Retired Greyhound as Pets (REGAP) (FL) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Home for Horses (UK) (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Home for Horses, Inc. (FL) (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Riverglen Feline Conservation Park (Arkansas) (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation (MT) (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Rondebult Bird Sanctuary (Canada) (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Russia: All-Russian Society for Nature Conservation (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Russia: Association for the Defense of Homeless Animals (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Russia: Center for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (CETA) (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Russia: Miscellaneous (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Russia: National Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Russia) - missing folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Russia: St. Petersburg Vegetarians (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Russia: Tallin Animal Protection Society (TAPS) (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Russia: Vegetarian Society of Russia (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Russian Society for the Protection of Animals (Russia) (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Save African Endangered Wildlife Foundation (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Save the Cow (FL) (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Save the Cow Fund (CA) (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Save the Florida Panther (FL) (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Save the Manatee Club (FL) (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - SC: International Primate Protection League (IPPL) (SC)- 1 of 5 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - SC: International Primate Protection League (IPPL) (SC)- 2 of 5 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - SC: International Primate Protection League (IPPL) (SC)- 3 of 5 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - SC: International Primate Protection League (IPPL) (SC)- 4 of 5 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - SC: International Primate Protection League (IPPL) (SC)- 5 of 5 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - SC: South Carolina Association for Marine Mammal Protection (SC) (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Scientists Center for Animal Welfare (DC) (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Scientists Group for Reform of Animal Experimentation (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (CA) 1 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (CA) 2 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Sea Turtle Center (CA) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Seal Beach Animal Care (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Shambala Preserve (CA) (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Shrine P. U. P. S. (People’s United Pet Support) (GA) (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Shubenacadie Wolf Center (Canada) (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Sierra Club (CA)- 1 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Sierra Club (CA)- 2 of 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Simian Lodge (VA) (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Simian Society (MO) (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Singapore Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Sociedad, La, Venezolana Protectora de Animales (locate) (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Society for Animal Protective Legislation (DC) 2” (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Society for the Conservation of Bighorn Sheep (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Society of Kind Understanding for Not Killing Skunks (SKUNKS) (CA) (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - South Africa: Afrikaans Articles (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - South Africa: Animal Voice of South Africa (South Africa) (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - South Africa: Beauty Without Cruesty S. A. (South Africa) (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - South Africa: Front for Animal Liberation and Conservation of Nature (FALCON) (South Africa) (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - South Africa: Miscellaneous/Other Groups/South Africa (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - South Africa: South African Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals (SAAAPEA) (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - South Africa: South Africans for the Abolition of Vivisection—Pretoria (SAAV) (South Africa) (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - South Florida Ferret Shelter (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Southern Ocean Whale Sanctuary (Antarctica) (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Spain Alternativa para la Liberación Animal (Spain) 1 ½” (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Spain Anti Bullfighting Campaign International (Spain) (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Spain Asociacion Nacional Para la Defensa de los Animales (Spain (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Spain Asociacion Para Un Trato Etico con Los Animales (ATEA) (Spain) (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Spain Association for the Defense of Animal Rights (Spain) (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Spain Coordinadora de Organizaciones de Defensa Ambiental (CODA) (Spain) (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Spain Miscellaneous/Spain (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Spain Spanish Articles - 1 of 4 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Spain Spanish Articles - 2 of 4 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Spain Spanish Articles - 3 of 4 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Spain Spanish Articles - 4 of 4 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Spay—USA (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - SPCA: Miscellaneous/SPCA/International (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis Herpetological Society (MO) (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Student Action Corps for Animals (DC) (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Students United Protesting Research on Sentient Subjects (SUPRESS) (CA) (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Sugarloaf Dolphin Sanctuary (FL) (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Suncoast Seabird Sanctuary (FL) (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Switzerland: International League of Doctors for the Abolition of Animal Experimentation (ILDAAE) (Switzerland) (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Switzerland: CIVIS (Switzerland) - 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Switzerland: CIVIS (Switzerland)- 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 14)